hello again folks so this is Matt and
再次向大家问好，这是马特，
we're talking about imperfect
我们在谈论不完美
information in the extensive form now so
现在以广泛的形式提供信息
we're going to be talking now about
我们现在要谈论
games where we have some sequential
我们有一些顺序的游戏
moves and there can be some uncertainty
移动，可能会有一些不确定性
in players minds about both the possible
在玩家心目中，两种可能性
payoffs of others and the strategies
他人的收益和策略
that others might be following
其他人可能会关注
so we'll start those just by you know to
所以我们将以您知道的方式开始
give you some ideas about this let's
给你一些想法，让我们
talk a little bit about poker which is a
谈一点关于扑克的知识
game has been becoming incredibly
游戏变得越来越不可思议
popular and recently both for people
受欢迎，最近都受到人们的欢迎
playing and on television and other
玩和看电视等
kinds of things and it's one of the
各种各样的东西，这是其中之一
oldest games which has very extensive
最古老的游戏
experience and for a lot of people and
经验，对很多人来说，
the the you know one of the critical
你知道的关键之一
aspects of poker is that there's
扑克方面是
actually sequential play in betting
实际上是连续下注
calling folding so one player gets you
召唤折叠，让一个玩家抓住你
know two to make a decision in terms of
认识两个人就
how much they're going to make a bet at
他们要下多少赌注
a certain point in time other players
在某个时间点其他玩家
have to react to that
必须对此做出反应
so the sequential play you see some
所以顺序播放，您会看到一些
cards in in many of these games but not
这些游戏中有很多是纸牌，但不是
all so you might see some of the cards
所有这些，所以您可能会看到一些卡片
that the other players are holding but
其他玩家正在举行，但
you don't know how strong their hand is
你不知道他们的手有多强
and you have to be inferring things
而你必须在推断事物
about their their possible cards both
关于他们可能的牌
from odds in the game and based on what
从游戏中的赔率以及基于什么
they're doing in terms of their strategy
他们正在根据自己的策略进行
so you see the bets and you react to
所以你看到了赌注，你对
them and you have to make inferences
他们，你必须做出推断
based on that so that involves having
基于此，这涉及到
beliefs about the motivations the
关于动机的信念
rationality of other players what their
其他玩家的合理性
payoffs are what their potential payoffs
收益是他们潜在的收益
are which in poker might come from from
扑克中的哪些可能来自
the cards so when we think about these
卡，所以当我们考虑这些
kinds of games you know there's many
您知道很多类型的游戏
possible hands that's gonna make poker a
可能使扑克成为可能
fairly complicated game to keep track of
相当复杂的游戏，以跟踪
there's many betting strategies which
有很多下注策略
means that the overall tree that we have
意味着我们拥有的整体树
to work with is gonna be quite
与之共事会相当
complicated so it's actually going to be
复杂，所以实际上
almost impossible to draw the tree in
几乎不可能画树
the sense of just
正义感
on the screen but there's nonetheless a
在屏幕上，但仍然有
lot that we can learn about analyzing
我们可以从分析中学到很多
such games and analyzing the types of
这类游戏并分析
strategies that they have how how do we
他们有如何做的策略
represent extensive form games with
代表广泛的形式游戏
incomplete information how might we but
不完整的信息我们怎么可能
reason about these things
这些事情的原因
and moreover there'll be simpler
而且会更简单
settings you know poker is actually a
您知道扑克的设置实际上是
fairly complicated game and there's
相当复杂的游戏，
other fairly complicated games but very
其他相当复杂的游戏，但非常
high stakes games so for instance you
高风险游戏，例如您
know we could have one country thinking
知道我们可以有一个国家的思考
about invading another one a potential
关于入侵另一个潜在的
war or a conflict there trying to decide
战争或冲突试图决定
what the other country is going to do in
另一个国家在做什么
response so if you invaded what would
回应，因此，如果您入侵了
they do that's a game of incomplete
他们这样做是不完整的游戏
information because you might not know
信息，因为您可能不知道
exactly how strong they are or how was
他们到底有多坚强
the the willingness of the population to
人口的意愿
fight what might happen politically how
对抗政治上可能发生的事情
how strong are they and if there was a
他们有多坚强，如果有
war so there's these are situations
战争，所以有这些情况
where one party might have to move first
一方可能必须先走的地方
anticipating reaction of the other the
期待对方的反应
second one has to anticipate what the
第二个必须预料到
the the fact they're being invaded means
他们受到入侵的事实意味着
about the strength of the other do you
关于对方的力量
surrender do you fight so those are
你投降了，所以那些
games that they're going to have similar
他们将拥有相似的游戏
kinds of features to these and it's
这些功能的特点是
gonna be very important to develop a set
开发一套非常重要
of a way of representing these things
代表这些东西的方式
and some thoughts about analyzing those
以及有关分析这些问题的一些想法
so that's where we're headed next and
这就是我们接下来要去的地方
we'll see more a lot more of this very
我们将在其中看到更多
shortly
不久